<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Silencio</string>
    <string name="nav_open">Navigation Open</string>
    <string name="nav_closed">Navigation Closed</string>


    <string name="help_text">Silencio is pretty simple to use.To create a new event press the + add button located at the top right corner which will show a new window for some information.
To select time tap twice in start time and end time field.

\n\nTo save an event fill up the required field then press the tick button located at the top right corner and to cancel
press the X cross button at the top left corner.
After saving an event it will appear in a list with the name,time and days.

\n\nTap on the event to edit or delete.

\n\nThere have a switch associated with each event by which one can control an event.
There is also a navigation drawer with some contents incuding themes,communication,help,exit;

\n\nThanks:)
    </string>

    <string name="bangla_help">
\n\nসিলিনসিও ব্যবহার করা খুবই সহজ।একটি নতুন ইভেন্ট তৈরী করার জন্য উপরের ডান কোনায় + বাটন টি চাপুন এটি কিছু তথ্যের জন্য নতুন উইন্ডও দেখাবে।
সময় নিরধারণের জন্য স্টার্ট টাইম এবং ইন্ড টাইম ক্ষেত্রে দুইবার চাপুন।

\n\nকোনও ইভেন্ট সংরক্ষণ করার জন্য প্রয়োজনীয় ক্ষেত্রটি পূরণ করুন পরে উপরের ডান কোণায় অবস্থিত টিক বাটন চাপুন এবং কেন্সেল করতে উপরের বাম কোণের  X বাটন চাপুন।
সংরক্ষণ করার পর ইভেন্টটি নাম,সময় এবং দিন সহ একটি লিস্টে থাকবে।

\n\nইডিট এবং ডিলিট করার জন্য ইভেন্টে স্পর্শ করুন।

\n\nপ্রত্যেকটি ইভেন্ট এর সাথে একটি করে সুইচ আছে যা দিয়ে একজন ইভেন্টটি কন্ট্রল করতে পারবে।
একটি ন্যাভিগেশন ড্রয়ার আছে যেখানে থেমস,কমিউনিকেশন,হেল্প,ইক্সিট নামে কিছু কন্টেনটস আছে।

\n\nধন্যবাদ:)
    </string>

    <string name="asfak">&#160;Name : Md Asfak Hussain Shafi
        \n Email : asfaklus2@gmail.com
        \n Department : CSE
        \n Institution : Leading University
    </string>
    <string name="sunny">
          &#160; Name : Sunny Saha
        \n Email : scsahasunny@gmail.com
        \n Department : CSE
        \n Institution : Leading University
    </string>
    <string name="husain">
         &#160;Name : Husain Ahmad
        \n Email : husainlus467@gmail.com
        \n Department : CSE
        \n Institution : Leading University
    </string>
</resources>
